<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to Nguyễn Trọng Nghĩa&#39;s page</title>
    <link>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Welcome to Nguyễn Trọng Nghĩa&#39;s page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Seventh Secret</title>
      <link>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/post/p3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/post/p3/</guid>
      <description>Secret about Adolf Part I Oxford historian Harrison Ashcroft, preparing to publish his biography of Adolf Hitler entitled Herr Hitler along with his daughter Emily Ashcroft, receives a letter from a stranger in West Berlin informing them that the book could be wrong if published with the popular version of Hitler&amp;rsquo;s suicide as its end. The stranger even writes that he can prove that the corpse shown in the April 30, 1945 photos of Führerbunker were not of Hitler and his wife Eva Braun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tài khoản của bạn đã bị hack</title>
      <link>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/post/p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/post/p1/</guid>
      <description>Creepy story Part I The girl who pushed open the shop door was too young for the cane she leaned on. I examined her from under the brim of my dark baker’s boy cap.
I sat in my tall swivel chair behind the counter, feet kicked up next to the register. Two knitting needles clicked in my lap, the motion so mechanical I never looked down. They manipulated the strand of yarn into a nearly-completed scarf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Health Organization</title>
      <link>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/post/p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/post/p2/</guid>
      <description>WHO About WHO The World Health Organization (WHO) is a specialized agency of the United Nations responsible for international public health.[1] It is part of the U.N. Sustainable Development Group. The WHO Constitution, which establishes the agency&amp;rsquo;s governing structure and principles, states its main objective as ensuring &amp;ldquo;the attainment by all peoples of the highest possible level of health.&amp;quot;[2] It is headquartered in Geneva, Switzerland, with six semi-autonomous regional offices and 150 field offices worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Typesetting</title>
      <link>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/post/math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/post/math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anhnghia47.github.io/Blog/about/</guid>
      <description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>